Guide to the Cindy Domingo Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1982-1992; 5651-002; 9 cubic feet 9 boxes
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 9)
    - Economics Information, 1976 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Extradition Treaty 1983, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Filipinos General Information, 1970-1992 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Filipino Community Seattle, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Filipino Immigration Statistics, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Filipino American National Historical Society, 1987 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Frontline Newspaper, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Frontline Workshop, 1986 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Gay Pride Day, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Goddard-Cambridge Core Courses, Undated (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Goddard-Cambridge Personal File, 1977 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - Independent Forum Southern Africa, 1979 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - JACL Banquet December, 1982 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Jesse Jackson Presidential Campaign, 1984 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Independent Forum Medicine Under Capitalism, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Union of Democratic Filipino (KDP) Independent Forum Andres Bonifacio Day, 1978 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Union of Democratic Filipino (KDP) Mailing List, Undated (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Union of Democratic Filipino (KDP) Independent Forum Philippine National Day, Undated (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Korea, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Korean Airliner Incident, 1983 (Box-folder 5/39)
    - Labor Summer School (AFL-CIO), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Law, Laura, Undated (Box-folder 5/41)
    - Leadership Conference 1980, Undated (Box-folder 5/42)
    - Maoism, 1981 (Box-folder 5/43)
    - Marxist Education Project, 1986 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - Marxist Leninist Education Project (1979-1980), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 5/45)
    - Marxist Leninist Education Project Conference August 1980. (Box-folder 5/46)
    - Marxist Leninist Education Project On Practice Stuff, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5/47)
    - Marxist Leninist Education Project Racial Contradistions, 1980 (Box-folder 5/48)
    - Seattle, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Marxist Leninist Education Project Underdevelopment, Undated (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Marxist Leninist Education Project Afghanistan, 1980 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Morikawa Event 1991, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - National Anti-Racist Organzing Committee Newsletter (Like It Is), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - National Democratic Curriculum, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - National Secretariat Meetings, 1974 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Native Americans, 1985 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - New People's Army, Undated (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Nuclear Free & Independent Pacific, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Pacific Rim Countries, 1985 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Palestine, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Palestine, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Pananaw Newsletter, 1983 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Party Building Material, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Philippine History Courses, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - Philippine National Day 1982, Undated (Box-folder 6/17)
    - Precinct Captain Materials, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Poland, Undated (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Proposition 13, 1979 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Race/National Question Study, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Santos Campaign, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - SAOC Theoretical Studies, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - 28390, 1977 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Silkwood Teach-In March, 1982, 1981 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Song Sheets, Undated (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Simpson/Mazzoli Bill, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - South Africa, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - Speakers References, 1991 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - Speeches, 1985 (Box-folder 6/30)
    - Star Wars Frontline Forum, 1985 (Box-folder 6/31)
    - Tactical Study on Contradiction, 1975 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Tactical Study on Practice, 1975 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - Tactical Study On the Relations of the Sexes, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 6/34)
    - Tactical Study Oppose Individualism, Undated (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Tactical Study Social Investigation, 1975 (Box-folder 6/36)
    - Tactical Study United Front, 1940-1975 (Box-folder 6/37)
    - Thailand, 1986 (Box-folder 6/38)
    - Theoretical School (1978) Medical Workshop, 1977 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Theoretical School 1980 (Box-folder 6/40)
    - Trade Union Seminar 1980, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 6/41)
    - Trend Conference, 1982 (Box-folder 6/42)
    - Vietnam/Kampuchea Struggle, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 6/43)
    - Vision Seattle, 1989 (Box-folder 6/44)
    - Weber Case, 1979 (Box-folder 6/45)
    - Woman Question Northern California Alliance Theoretical School, 1979 (Box-folder 6/46)
    - Youth, 1980 (Box-folder 6/47)
    - Chinese Youth Gangs, 1972 (Box-folder 6/48)
    - Women Third World Women's Class, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 6/49)
    - Women, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 6/50)
    - Women Third World Women's Class - Goddard, 1977 (Box-folder 6/51)
    - Civil Rights Bill of 1990 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Civil Rights Bill of 1990 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Labor Aristocracy Conference, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Far West Convention, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - 1978 Filipino People's Far West Convention (Box-folder 7/5)
    - 1977 Pilipino People's Far West Convention, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Katipunan ng mga Demokratikong Pilipino, 1979 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Riceroots Leaders and Public Information - Seminar 1982, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - 12th Annual Filipino People's Far West Convention, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - State of the Trend Conference December, 1982 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Third World Women's Alliance Reports and Materials, 1980 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Nuclear Disarmament Conference March, 1983, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Letelier Teach-In, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - People of Color and AIDS: Meeting the Challenge of the Decade, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Transformation of Military Government to Civil Government, c. 1980s (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Papers, Presentations, and News Articles, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Campaign For Democracy and Independence 14th National Conference, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - 10th National Conference Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship/Philippine Solidarity Network, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - 11th National Conference Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship/Philippine Solidarity Network, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - First Filipino American State Congress (1 of 2), 1984 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - First Filipino American State Congress: Kadiwa (2 of 2), 1984 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Committee to Advance The Movement for Democracy and Independence 13th National Conference, 1987 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - 12th National Conference Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship/Philippine Solidarity Network, 1986 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Philippine News, 1979 (Box-folder 7/24)
    - Philippines, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 7/25)
    - Journal 1, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 7/26)
    - Journal 2, 1983 (Box-folder 7/27)
    - Journal 3, 1983 (Box-folder 7/28)
    - Journal 4, 1981 (Box-folder 7/29)
    - Journal 5, 1982 (Box-folder 7/30)
    - A Documentary Exhibit on Pioneer Filipino Cannery Workers: Alaskeros, 1988 (Box-folder 7/31)
    - Seattle Post-Intelligencer What's Happening, 1987 (Box-folder 7/32)
    - Notepad, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 7/33)
    - Philippines, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Christmas Carolling Campaign, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Far West Convention, 1981 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Extradition Treaty, 1982 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Elections - 2/7/86, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Political Prisoners Project, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - AIDS (Philippines), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - ANG Printing, 1985 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - ASEAN, 1986 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - August 21, 1985 Event (Box-folder 8/10)
    - August 27th March, 1983 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Church, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Non-Alignment Movement, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Economy, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Fact Sheets, 1982 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Gabriela, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - General Amnesty Campaign, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Human Rights, 1991 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Kilusang Mayo Uno Tour 9/24-9/28/85, 1985 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Labor, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Military AID U.S. to Philippines, 1985 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Monographs, 1984 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - National Federation of Sugar Workers, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - National Democratic Front of the Philippines Update, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Non-Alignment, 1986 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Philippine Liberation Courier, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Philippine Research Center Newsletter, 1977 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Philippine Informational Bulletin (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Philippine Informational Bulletin (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - Philippine Miscellaneous Information, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Rainforests, 1991 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - "Rustling of Leaves", 1988 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - Santiago, Irene Tour, 1984 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - 31312, 1985 (Box-folder 8/34)
    - Sex Industry/Tourism, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 8/35)
    - Vigilante Groups/Activities, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 8/36)
    - U.S. Bases in the Philippines, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 8/37)
    - Westinghouse Nuclear Reactor, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 8/38)
    - Women Filipino Women (1 of 2), 1976-1989 (Box-folder 8/39)
    - Women Filipino Women (2 of 2), 1982-1987 (Box-folder 8/40)
    - Peace & Solidarity, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Frontline 4/11/1983 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Frontline 6/27/1983 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Frontline 7/11/1983 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Frontline 8/8/1983 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Frontline 8/22/1983 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Frontline 9/19/1983 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Frontline 10/3/1983 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Frontline 10/17/1983 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Frontline 10/131/1983 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Frontline 11/14/1983 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Frontline 11/28/1983 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Frontline 12/12/1983 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Frontline 12/26/1983 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Frontline 1/23/1984 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Frontline 2/6/1984 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Frontline 2/20/1984 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Frontline 1984 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Frontline 3/19/1984 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Frontline 4/2/1984 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Frontline 4/16/1984 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Frontline 4/30/1984 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Frontline 5/14/1984 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Frontline 5/28/1984 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Frontline 6/25/1984 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Frontline 7/9/1984 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Frontline 7/23/1984 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Frontline 8/6/1984 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Frontline 8/20/1984 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Frontline 9/17/1984 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - Frontline 10/29/1984 (Box-folder 9/31)
    - Frontline 11/19/1984 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Frontline 12/31/1984 (Box-folder 9/33)
    - Frontline 1/21/1985 (Box-folder 9/34)
    - Frontline 2/4/1985 (Box-folder 9/35)
    - Frontline 2/18/1985 (Box-folder 9/36)
    - Palestine Focus January-Feburary 1985 (Box-folder 9/37)
    - Frontline 3/4/1985 (Box-folder 9/38)
    - Frontline 3/18/1985 (Box-folder 9/39)
    - Frontline 4/1/1985 (Box-folder 9/40)
    - Frontline 4/15/1985 (Box-folder 9/41)
    - Frontline 4/29/1985 (Box-folder 9/42)
    - Frontline 5/13/1985 (Box-folder 9/43)
    - Frontline 5/27/1985 (Box-folder 9/44)
    - Frontline 6/24/1985 (Box-folder 9/45)
    - Frontline 7/8/1985 (Box-folder 9/46)
    - Frontline 8/5/1985 (Box-folder 9/47)
    - Frontline 8/19/1985 (Box-folder 9/48)
    - Frontline 10/14/1985 (Box-folder 9/49)
    - Frontline 10/28/1985 (Box-folder 9/50)
    - Frontline 11/11/1985 (Box-folder 9/51)
    - Frontline 11/25/1985 (Box-folder 9/52)
    - Alaskero News 12/1985 (Box-folder 9/53)
    - Frontline 12/9/1985 (Box-folder 9/54)
    - Frontline 12/23/1985 (Box-folder 9/55)
    - Frontline 1/20/1986 (Box-folder 9/56)
    - Frontline 2/3/1986 (Box-folder 9/57)
    - Frontline 3/3/1986 (Box-folder 9/58)
    - Frontline 3/17/1986 (Box-folder 9/59)
    - Frontline 3/31/1986 (Box-folder 9/60)
    - Frontline 4/14/1986 (Box-folder 9/61)
    - Frontline 4/28/1986 (Box-folder 9/62)
    - Frontline 5/12/1986 (Box-folder 9/63)
    - Frontline 5/26/1986 (Box-folder 9/64)
    - Frontline 6/9/1986 (Box-folder 9/65)
    - Frontline 7/7/1986 (Box-folder 9/66)
    - Frontline 7/21/1986 (Box-folder 9/67)
    - Frontline 8/18/1986 (Box-folder 9/68)
    - Frontline 9/1/1986 (Box-folder 9/69)
    - Frontline 9/29/1986 (Box-folder 9/70)
    - Frontline 10/13/1986 (Box-folder 9/71)
    - Frontline 10/27/1986 (Box-folder 9/72)
    - Frontline 11/10/1986 (Box-folder 9/73)
    - Frontline 12/8/1986 (Box-folder 9/74)
    - Frontline 1/19/1987 (Box-folder 9/75)
    - Frontline 2/2/1987 (Box-folder 9/76)
    - Frontline 2/16/1987 (Box-folder 9/77)
    - Frontline 3/2/1987 (Box-folder 9/78)
    - Frontline 3/16/1987 (Box-folder 9/79)
    - Frontline 3/30/1987 (Box-folder 9/80)
    - Frontline 4/13/1987 (Box-folder 9/81)
    - Frontline 5/11/1987 (Box-folder 9/82)
    - Frontline 5/25/1987 (Box-folder 9/83)
    - Frontline 6/8/1987 (Box-folder 9/84)
    - Frontline 7/6/1987 (Box-folder 9/85)
    - Frontline 7/20/1987 (Box-folder 9/86)
    - Frontline 8/17/1987 (Box-folder 9/87)
    - Frontline 8/31/1987 (Box-folder 9/88)
    - Frontline 9/28/1987 (Box-folder 9/89)
    - Frontline 10/12/1987 (Box-folder 9/90)
    - Frontline 10/26/1987 (Box-folder 9/91)
    - Frontline 11/23/1987 (Box-folder 9/92)
    - Frontline 12/7/1987 (Box-folder 9/93)
    - Frontline 12/21/1987 (Box-folder 9/94)
    - Frontline 1/18/1988 (Box-folder 9/95)
    - Frontline 2/1/1988 (Box-folder 9/96)
    - Frontline 2/15/1988 (Box-folder 9/97)
    - Frontline 2/29/1988 (Box-folder 9/98)
    - Frontline 3/14/1988 (Box-folder 9/99)
    - Frontline 3/28/1988 (Box-folder 9/100)
    - Frontline 4/11/1988 (Box-folder 9/101)
    - Frontline 6/20/1988 (Box-folder 9/102)
    - Frontline 7/4/1988 (Box-folder 9/103)
    - Frontline 7/18/1988 (Box-folder 9/104)
    - Frontline 8/1/1988 (Box-folder 9/105)
    - Frontline 8/15/1988 (Box-folder 9/106)
    - Frontline 8/29/1988 (Box-folder 9/107)
    - Frontline 10/10/1988 (Box-folder 9/108)
    - Frontline 10/24/1988 (Box-folder 9/109)
    - Frontline 11/7/1988 (Box-folder 9/110)
    - Frontline 12/5/1988 (Box-folder 9/111)
    - Frontline 12/19/1988 (Box-folder 9/112)
    - Frontline 1/16/1989 (Box-folder 9/113)
    - Frontline 1/30/1989 (Box-folder 9/114)
    - Frontline 2/13/1989 (Box-folder 9/115)
    - Frontline 3/13/1989 (Box-folder 9/116)
    - Frontline 3/27/1989 (Box-folder 9/117)
    - Frontline 4/10/1989 (Box-folder 9/118)
    - Frontline 4/24/1989 (Box-folder 9/119)
    - Frontline 5/22/1989 (Box-folder 9/120)
    - Frontline 6/19/1989 (Box-folder 9/121)
    - Frontline 7/3/1989 (Box-folder 9/122)
    - Frontline 7/17/1989 (Box-folder 9/123)
    - Frontline 8/14/1989 (Box-folder 9/124)
    - Frontline 8/28/1989 (Box-folder 9/125)
    - A South African Revolution in the Making, 1984 (Box-folder 9/126)
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1973-2009; 5651-003; 16 cubic feet 16 boxes
  Donor: Cindy Domingo, August 31, 2012.
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 16)
    - Equality for Women, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Community to Community (C2C), 2002-2009 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Death Penalty, 2005 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Ade Domingo Life Story, Undated (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Flyer: Welcome to Domingo Viernes Apartments at Village Square II (Low Income Housing), 2004 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - International Examiner, 2003 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Equal Voice for America's Families, 2009 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Filipino American National Historical Society (FANHS), 2010 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Bob Hasegawa's State Representative Campaign, 2004 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - National Lawyers Guild Newsletter of the Labor & Employment Committee, 2009 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Gender, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Got Green Environmental Program, 2008 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Immigration, 2003-2011 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Immigration & African Americans, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - History of International District, 2008 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - International Examiner, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - International Examiner CVA, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Community Organizing in International District, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - International Examiner/Grants, 2010 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - International Women's Day/Peace & Justice, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - International Women's Day, 2005 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - International Women's Day/Peace & Justice, 2008 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - International Women's Day, 2010 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - International Women's Day, 2011 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Latin America, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. March and Rally, 2010 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. March and Rally, 2011 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Alex Domingo Maynard, 2009 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Deaths and commemoration of male activists, 2004-2011 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum Seattle, 2006-2010 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum Meetings/Workshops, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum National Governing Board Meeting, 2007 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum Guiding Principles, 2008 (Box-folder 1/34)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum & International Examiner, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 1/37)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum Originals, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 1/38)
    - Aquino Assassination, 1983 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Pananani Talita, 1983 (Box-folder 1/40)
    - Simpson-Mazzoli, 1983 (Box-folder 1/41)
    - Solidarity Newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/42)
    - U.S. Anti-Imperialist League Studies, 1982 (Box-folder 1/43)
    - Repressive Legislation-Marcos, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/44)
    - National Democracy & Socialism, 1967 (Box-folder 1/45)
    - Alaskero News, 1983 (Box-folder 1/46)
    - Davao City Political Prisoners-Marcos, 1983 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP), 1983 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Marcos Opposition-Filipino Solidarity, 1983 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Extradition Treaty, 1983 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Filipino Housing-Seattle Events, 1976 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Calendars, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship/Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN), 1983- (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Pasko, 1975 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - NW Filipino People's Farwest Convention, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Barrio Fiesta, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - National Security-War Economy, 1984 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - First National Conference-Filipino Immigrant Rights, 1980 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship-Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN), Housing, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - National Filipino Immigrant Rights Organization (NFIRO), 1981 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP)/CAMD Reports, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Far Eastern Economic Review, Part 1 of 6, 1984 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Far Eastern Economic Review, Part 2 of 6, 1984 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Far Eastern Economic Review, Part 3 of 6, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Far Eastern Economic Review, Part 4 of 6, 1985 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Far Eastern Economic Review, Part 5 of 6, 1985 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Far Eastern Economic Review, Part 6 of 6, 1985 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - National Filipino Commission/Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Memos & Reports, 1987 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP), Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship-Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN), 1981-1984 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Petitions, 1985 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Slide Show Descriptions, Undated (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Tourism & Women, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Philippine Labor/Workers, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Worker Deaths/Marcos Demonstrations, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 2/28)
    - NW Filipino People's Farwest Convention: Tagapaglikha, 1981 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship-Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN), 1982-1987 (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Labor Campaign, 1985 (Box-folder 2/31)
    - Newsletter of the National Filipino Immigrant Rights Organization (NFIRO), 1981 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Philippine News Articles, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Ang Katipunan: National Newspaper of the Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP), 1981 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - International District Skit Scripts, Undated (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Filipino Postal Workers/United Filipino Organization (UFO), 1981 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Alaskero News, Undated (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Filipinos for Action & Reform (FAR), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship-Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN) Press Releases, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Friends of the Filipino People (FFP), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Vincent Lawsin Petitions (Filipino Community of Seattle), Undated (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship-Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN) Mailing lists blank, Undated (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Women's Outreach/Birth Control, 1981 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Philippine Labor Alert, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - WACPAC skit script, 1986 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Women and Labor, 1980 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Pilipino American Alliance and KDP- Muslim-Filipinos, Undated (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos/Immigrant Rights Notes, 1979 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Nurses Licensure Campaign, 1977 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Narciso-Perez, 1977 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Filipino Women, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - KDP Plan, Undated (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Kilusang Mayo Uno (KMU) (May First Movement), 1984 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Philippine Labor Fact Sheets, 1982 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Labor Materials, Undated (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Filipino Strikers/Marcos, 1985 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Women Workers, 1981 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Labor Slideshow, Undated (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Kilusang Mayo Uno (KMU) (May First Movement), 1984 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Task Force On Philippine Labor, 1985 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - Philippine Report/Labor Profiles, 1985 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Aquino Assassination/Marcos, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Labor Cover Letter, 1982 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - Friends of the Filipino People (FFP), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 3/33)
    - Seattle Newspaper articles August 22-September 1983 (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Seattle Newspaper articles, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - Fire Tree: Prison Poems from the Philippines, 1985 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - Conditions of the Filipino People Under Martial Law, 1979 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - Development Debacle: The World Bank in the Philippines. San Francisco, CA: Institute for Food and Development Policy; Philippine Solidarity Network, 1982 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - Hayes, P., Zarsky, L., & Bello, W. F. (1986). American lake: Nuclear peril in the Pacific. Ringwood, Vic., Australia: Penguin Books. (Box-folder 3/39)